https://www.rollerdie.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
804-5571
Exceptional Quality. Unmatched Service.
HomeAbout UsRoll Forming AdvantageCustom Roll Formed ShapesCustom Roll Formed TubesOur Tooling PartsCapabilitiesRoll FormingStampingPress BrakePowder CoatingWelding & BendingExtrusion ServicesSolar MountsFabricationAssemblyFinishingRoll Forming FAQIndustriesBlogContact UsCareersRequest a Quote
Search for:
Privacy Policy
Home/Privacy Policy
We value the importance of your personal privacy as it applies to your visit to our web site.  This site uses Insite Metrics and Google Analytics which are both metrics software that collect data about site visitors.
What We Collect
What website you came from to get here.
How long you stay for.
What kind of computer you’re using.
Anonymous and personal data, depending on what you do during your visit adn on what personal information you elect to give us.
What We Share
We do not sell, lease or otherwise share any personal information about our visitors with or to any third party companies or individuals.
We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on this company; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of our company or (c) act to protect the personal safety of the employees of our company and other users of the web site.
What We Use
“Cookies”
We use cookies to store information about your activities on our web site. We use this information to anonymously track your visit to our site. Even if you elect to give us personal information, that information will never appear in the cookies. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies.You can disable cookies (consult support information from your browser’s publisher). If you disable cookies, your visit to our site will not be significantly effected though, from time to time, we may provide special features that require the use of cookies.
JavaScript
We use JavaScript to enhance our web site and to assist in the tracking of anonymous data.If you disable JavaScript, many of the features on our web site will not work.
Web Beacons (Clear Gifs)
We may use “Web Beacons” together with cookies to track your activities on our web site through Insite Metrics. Generally, Web Beacons allow third party agents (tracking technology providers) to track web site activity on behalf of their customers. Our “Web Beacons” are designed to provide no tracking information in cases where a visitor’s cookies are disabled. Our use of Web Beacons conforms to or exceeds the Network Advertising Initiative’s Web Beacon Guidelines.
Web Server Log Files
We use web server log files to gather summary information about activities on our web site. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, internet service provider (ISP), referring documents, and operating system. We analyze this information to extract trends such as popular search engines and search terms and popular referrers . We also use this information to maintain the successful operation of our web servers. We do not use web server log files to track either anonymous or identifiable users.
What do we do with your data?
The tracking information allows us to better understand the kind of people who come to our site and what content they’re reading. This allows us to make better decisions about design and writing.
All of our activity related to Google Analytics use falls within the bounds of the Google Analytics Terms of Service.
Want to opt out of tracking?
You can opt out of Google’s advertising tracking cookie or use a browser plugin to opt out of all Google Analytics tracking software.
